KAH YEE CHIANG

Kuala Lumpur | kahyee.chiang@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/kahyeechiang

SUMMARY

Product manager bringing global experience from living in 7 countries and working on consumer and enterprise products at various startups and multinationals. My experience building my new university as part of the inaugural class has instilled my passion for building user-centric products and technologies.

EXPERIENCE

Scoop Technologies • San Francisco, CA

Aug 2019 - April 2020

Associate Product Manager

- Led on-time development (concept testing, tech planning, eng implementation) of the first enterprise feature
 to be rolled out to all of Scoop's Fortune 100 customers which would unlock moving customers from a
 trip-based pricing model to a platform-based SaaS pricing model by visualizing ROI; Wrote and evolved
 product requirements based on design and technical feedback with alignment from CPO and CRO
- Spearheaded a complex architectural addition to the underlying technical definitions of customers, which
 required backend, frontend, data/ETL work, by partnering with Chief Architect; conducted internal user
 research interviews and mocked up wireframes
- Conducted user research, journey mapping, and user acquisition funnel analysis of enterprise buyers and inbound leads and presented findings to VP of Marketing and CPO
- Managed and prioritized 40+ accessibility bugs; implemented 80+ XML copy changes across iOS and Android
- Build and deployed a no-code app to ~700 users across multiple markets and geographies by collaborating with product marketing for copy, visuals, user segmentation and targeting, and deployment
- Conducted technical research to evaluate capabilities of third party integrations (Bill.com, Checkr) to unblock
 the launch of ~40k new potential users at 3 new markets

Rockerbox • Remote

Oct 2018 - April 2019

Product Growth Associate

- Prospect new attribution sales clients and managed leads pipeline in Salesforce
- Owned optimizing paid search marketing campaigns on Google AdWords

Maker Media • San Francisco, CA

May 2018 - Aug 2019

Product Management Intern

- Conducted user research and competitive landscape analysis and suggested new product vision and roadmap priorities to CEO and internal stakeholders for digital learning product
- Analyzed NPS score data to provide recommendations, using multivariate regressions, decision trees, and pivot tables in R

Cox Communications • Remote

Oct 2017 - April 2018

Product Development Consultant

Created and tested 3 prototypes as part of an exploration of a new product line, reported to the VP of Strategic
 Planning & Analysis

EDUCATION

Minerva Schools at KGI • Summa Cum Laude, GPA: 3.8/4.0

2015 - 2019